{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Few people in our village ___ afford to buy a car.",
      "a": "must",
      "b": "need",
      "c": "may",
      "d": "can",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Can: Show ability to do something or how to do something\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Take an umbrella with you lest it _________ rain.",
      "a": "should",
      "b": "would",
      "c": "did",
      "d": "might",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Should: used to say that you expect something to happen or be true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He stepped aside so that the fat lady ___ pass by.",
      "a": "will",
      "b": "can",
      "c": "might",
      "d": "used to",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- Might: if something might happen or might be true, there is a possibility that it may happen or may be true, but you are not at all certain",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is one of the most tragic facts in the recent development of science that the conquest of the air, which on all grounds ___ towards the unification of the world and the harmony of mankind, has actually become our most threatening danger.",
      "a": "would have worked",
      "b": "could have worked",
      "c": "should have worked",
      "d": "will have worked",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Should + Present Perfect Tense to comment about a past action which didn't happen in the best way. The speaker supposes that the past action would have turned out better if the recommended action had been followed.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "A computer ___ think for itself; it must be told what to do.",
      "a": "couldn't",
      "b": "can't",
      "c": "might not",
      "d": "may not",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Can: Show ability to do something or how to do something\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Could I borrow your helmet? \"Yes, of course you ___ .\"",
      "a": "will",
      "b": "might",
      "c": "should",
      "d": "can",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Can: to be allowed to do something or to have the right or power to do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "James ___ go with us tomorrow morning, but he isn't very sure yet.",
      "a": "to be cleaned",
      "b": "to clean",
      "c": "be cleaned",
      "d": "clean",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Clean: used to emphasize the fact that an action or movement is complete and thorough (=complete)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Could we call you by your nickname? \"Yes, you ___.\"",
      "a": "could",
      "b": "will",
      "c": "was able to",
      "d": "may",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Will:  used like 'can' to show what is possible",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Could you lend me a pen? \"Yes, ___,\"",
      "a": "Would",
      "b": "might",
      "c": "may",
      "d": "can",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- Might: used to suggest politely what someone should do\n\n",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "From what I hear about their trip, their hotel and the weather, they _________ their holidays very much.",
      "a": "shouldn't have enjoyed",
      "b": "would have enjoyed",
      "c": "can't have enjoyed",
      "d": "needn't have enjoyed",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n-Need (British English):  used in negative sentences when saying that something is not necessary or not always true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}